Katarzyna Żukowska

Product Designer

+4571498925 / +48698470497

kejtizuki@gmail.com https://kejtizuki.github.io/portfolio https://www.linkedin.com/in/k-zukowska/ I'm a Product Designer working in all phases of design. I understand the nuances of implementation and enjoy working together with the developers to build digital experiences. I love working on complex products and finding my way through ambiguity. I aim to deliver coherent visual language with smooth interactions.

Experience

User Experience Designer | Issuu, Copenhagen

09 / 2019 - Present (2 years)

Working on SaaS core features in *all product phases*. Currently leading Creator Content project and building the new Design System. Defined the foundation for Issuu's redesign in collaboration with a lead designer. Worked on improving the reading experience on a mobile platform and redesigned analytics page.

User Experience Intern | Designit, Copenhagen

03 / 2019 - 08 / 2019 (6 months)

Involved in various projects related to UI / UX design and research.

Frontend Developer | Dixa, Copenhagen

08 / 2018 - 03 / 2019 (8 months)

Contributed to developing customer service software. Coded the main features of the platform using HTML, CSS and React. Worked on CSS animations, responsive layouts and design system components.

Student Research Assistant | Cachet, Copenhagen

08 / 2018 - 03 / 2019 (9 months)

Designed and developed Internet-based Cognitive Assessment Tool (ICAT) - a web-based tool that assesses verbal memory, working memory, and psychomotor speed.

Web UI Developer | IBM, Krakow

02 / 2017 - 07 / 2017 (6 months)

Implemented and co-designed frontend part of an internal platform designed for IBM Finance Department.

Education

MSc Digital Media Engineering | DTU - Technical University of Denmark

2017 - 2019

Thesis topic: "Design and User Study of Interactive Visualization Techniques for Personal Data Time-Series". Received the highest grade.

Creative Technology (Erasmus exchange) University of Twente

2016

BEng Computer Science AGH University of Science and Technology

2013 - 2017

Skills

UX Design

Sketching, Wireframing, Interactive Prototyping, User Flows, User Journeys

UI Design

Visual Design, Design Systems, UI Kits, Basic branding experience

Research

User interviews, Personas, Usability studies

Frontend development

HTML, CSS, React, d3.js

Languages

English (C1), Spanish (B1), German (A2), Polish (native)